<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/css" href="uslm.css"?><bill xmlns="http://schemas.gpo.gov/xml/uslm" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/" xsi:schemaLocation="http://schemas.gpo.gov/xml/uslm https://www.govinfo.gov/schemas/xml/uslm/uslm-2.0.5.xsd" xml:lang="en">
<!--Disclaimer: Legislative measures that include compacts or other non-standard data structures will require additional modeling and may contain inconsistencies in the converted USLM XML.-->
<meta><dc:title>114 HR 5065 ENR: To direct the Administrator of the Transportation Security Administration to notify air carriers and security screening personnel of the Transportation Security Administration of such Administration’s guidelines regarding permitting baby formula, breast milk, purified deionized water, and juice on airplanes, and for other purposes.</dc:title>
<dc:type>House Bill</dc:type><docNumber>5065</docNumber><citableAs>114 HR 5065 ENR</citableAs>
<citableAs>114hr5065enr</citableAs>
<citableAs>114 H.R. 5065 ENR</citableAs>
<dc:creator>United States House of Representatives</dc:creator><dc:publisher>United States Government Publishing Office</dc:publisher><dc:format>text/xml</dc:format><dc:language>EN</dc:language><dc:rights>Pursuant to Title 17 Section 105 of the United States Code, this file is not subject to copyright protection and is in the public domain.</dc:rights><docStage>ENR</docStage>
<processedBy>GPO Locator to USLM Converter 3.7.10;Stage2.20201027</processedBy><processedDate>2020-12-28</processedDate>
<congress>114</congress><session>2</session><publicPrivate>public</publicPrivate>
</meta>
<preface><dc:type>H. R.</dc:type><docNumber>5065</docNumber>

<congress style="-uslm-lc:I665502" value="114">One Hundred Fourteenth Congress of the United States of America</congress><session style="-uslm-lc:I665503" value="2">AT THE SECOND SESSION</session>
<enrolledDateline style="-uslm-lc:I665504">Begun and held at the City of Washington on Monday, the fourth day of January, two thousand and sixteen</enrolledDateline>
</preface>
<main>
<longTitle>
<docTitle style="-uslm-lc:I665505" class="centered fontsize18">An Act</docTitle>
<officialTitle style="-uslm-lc:I665511" class="centered fontsize8">To direct the Administrator of the Transportation Security Administration to notify air carriers and security screening personnel of the Transportation Security Administration of such Administration’s guidelines regarding permitting baby formula, breast milk, purified deionized water, and juice on airplanes, and for other purposes.<?GPOvSpace 08?></officialTitle>
</longTitle>
<enactingFormula style="-uslm-lc:I650120">  Be it enacted by the Senate and House of Representa­tives of the United States of America in Congress assembled,</enactingFormula>
<section identifier="/us/bill/114/hr/5065/s1" id="d70e81" style="-uslm-lc:I650146"><num value="1">SECTION 1. </num><heading>SHORT TITLE.</heading><content style="-uslm-lc:I650120">  This Act may be cited as the “<shortTitle role="act">Bottles and Breast­feeding Equipment Screening Act</shortTitle>”.</content>
</section>
<section identifier="/us/bill/114/hr/5065/s2" id="d70e93" style="-uslm-lc:I650141"><num value="2">SEC. 2. </num><heading>TSA SECURITY SCREENING GUIDELINES FOR BABY FORMULA, BREAST MILK, PURIFIED DEIONIZED WATER FOR INFANTS, AND JUICE ON AIRPLANES; TRAINING ON SPECIAL PROCEDURES.</heading>
<chapeau style="-uslm-lc:I650120" class="indent0 fontsize10">  Not later than 90 days after the date of the enactment of this Act, the Administrator of the Transportation Security Administration shall—</chapeau><paragraph identifier="/us/bill/114/hr/5065/s2/1" id="d70e101" style="-uslm-lc:I650122" class="indent1 fontsize10"><num value="1" style="-uslm-lc:emspace2">(1) </num><content>notify air carriers and security screening personnel of the Transportation Security Administration and personnel of private security companies providing security screening pursuant to <ref href="/us/usc/t49/s44920">section 44920 of title 49, United States Code</ref>, of such Administration’s guidelines regarding permitting baby formula, breast milk, purified deionized water for infants, and juice on airplanes under the Administration’s guidelines known as the 3–1–1 Liquids Rule Exemption; and</content>
</paragraph>
<paragraph identifier="/us/bill/114/hr/5065/s2/2" id="d70e111" style="-uslm-lc:I650122" class="indent1 fontsize10"><num value="2" style="-uslm-lc:emspace2">(2) </num><content>in training procedures for security screening personnel of the Administration and private security companies providing security screening pursuant to <ref href="/us/usc/t49/s44920">section 44920 of title 49, United States Code</ref>, include training on special screening procedures.</content>
</paragraph>
</section>
</main>
<signatures>
<signature><role style="-uslm-lc:I650114">Speaker of the House of Representatives.</role></signature>
<signature><role style="-uslm-lc:I650114">Vice President of the United States and  President of the Senate.</role></signature>
</signatures>
</bill>
